<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<diff>
    <add sel="/language[@id='44']">
        <page id="996666" title="ship" descr="ship" voice="yes">
            <t id="1">AEGS Javelin</t>
            <t id="2">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Javelin is a destroyer utilized by the United Empire of Earth Navy (UEEN). Designed as a modular spacecraft, the UEEN could make major conversions to the Javelin for different roles rather than constructing individual specialized capital ships. Javelins are used as convoy escorts, fleet support, orbital fire suppression, reconnaissance in force, and fast interception missions. Surplus Javelins have been sold on the civilian market. The ship features a total of five decks, each with a variety of crew positions and areas to explore and utilize.</t>
            <t id="3">ANVL F8C</t>
            <t id="4">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil F8C Lightning is the civilian variant of the F8A Lightning space superiority fighter that is used by the United Empire of Earth Navy. It closely mimics the military specs of the original F8A, and has been used in lines of defense against Vanduul invaders. It was made available in extremely limited numbers to the civilian market by Anvil to celebrate the debut of the F8A in the UEE Navy.</t>
            <t id="5">ANVL F8A</t>
            <t id="6">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil F8A Lightning is a heavy fighter employed by the UEE Navy to support space superiority. It was specifically designed to counter heavy Vanduul craft, such as the Glaive and Scythe. It is a more nimble and heavily armed fighter craft than its F7 predecessor, trading off a second turret for more fixed weaponry. Use of the F8A Lightning is generally restricted to elite UEEN squadrons, though the F8C Lightning civilian variant is beginning to see greater adoption.</t>
            <t id="7">RSIN Bengal</t>
            <t id="8">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: RSI&amp;#xA; Description: The Bengal is a fleet carrier spacecraft manufactured by Roberts Space Industries (RSI) for the United Empire of Earth Navy (UEEN). Bengal-class carriers carry multiple squadrons of fighters, bombers and support craft, and typically form the nucleus of a UEEN battle fleet or task force group. Their massive armaments and extremely heavy shielding make it nearly impossible for any individual craft to threaten them. It is 990 meters in length.</t>
            <t id="9">AEGS Hammerhead</t>
            <t id="10">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Hammerhead is a fast, sub-capital patrol gunship bristling with six manned quad-linked turrets. These turrets are optimized for anti-fighter and anti-ordnance work and grant the ship an unparalleled ability to put up a hailstorm of firepower that swiftly removes smaller aerospace threats. The Hammerhead is thus well suited for supporting larger capital ships in a fleet or to act as a general patrol vessel in lower-intensity theaters.</t>
            <t id="11">UEE Retribution</t>
            <t id="12">Size: S4&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: UEE&amp;#xA; Description: The Retribution-class super dreadnought is the largest capital ship constructed by UEE and multiple ship manufacturers to take part in the Vanduul War. The UEES Retribution is the only known ship of this class that has been built. The ship is envisioned by Admiral Bishop as a vital missing piece of the Navy's ship roster to combat Vanduul Kingships. A single Retribution class vessel was built at the UEE Naval Skydocks on MacArthur and is armed with multiple Behring 130mm &quot;Ship Buster&quot; rail guns.</t>
            <t id="13">AEGS Retaliator</t>
            <t id="14">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Retaliator is the base variant of the heavy bomber used by the UEE Military for centuries. It is a key portion of the UEE's power projection, Retaliator squadrons have served with distinction against outlaws, the Vanduul and elsewhere. The base version of the Retaliator is customizable with additional modules.</t>
            <t id="15">RSIN Scorpius</t>
            <t id="16">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: RSI&amp;#xA; Description: The Scorpius is a dual-seat heavy fighter manufactured by Roberts Space Industries (RSI). With an adaptable bi-wing configuration and revolutionary rail-mounted remote turret, the Scorpius offers unprecedented fire coverage, allowing for both defensive and assault-minded applications.</t>
            <t id="17">DRAK Kraken</t>
            <t id="18">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: DRAK&amp;#xA; Description: The Drake Kraken is designated as a Multi-role Light Carrier. With comfortable habs for a full crew, mammoth cargo capacity, and enough armament to blow even the most daunting frigate out of the sky. This self-sustaining flying fortress is the most ambitious project Drake has ever undertaken, and a testament to the empowerment of the people.</t>
            <t id="19">AEGS Idris-M</t>
            <t id="20">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Idris-M (Idris Military) is a frigate used by the UEE Military. It lends its name to the standard line of frigates in the United Empire of Earth Navy (UEEN). Idrises are larger than traditional corvettes, but smaller than destroyers and destroyer escorts. They can be found in most active battle group formations in the Human military. They are used for everything from long duration patrols to scouting dangerous jump points to interdiction. In addition to typical capital weaponry, Idris-class ships maintain a flight deck and a small spacecraft detachment of 2 medium fighters and one Argo MPUV-1C in a dedicated bay, although it designed to accommodate 3 medium fighters.</t>
            <t id="21">RSIN Scorpius Antares</t>
            <t id="22">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: RSI&amp;#xA; Description: The Scorpius Antares is a variant of the Scorpius heavy fighter, equipped with a co-pilot operated EMP device and quantum jammer in place of its turret. Specializing in short-range takedowns and squad-focused attacks, the Antares is a powerful utility fighter that can disable and trap enemy vessels while continuing to output significant firepower.</t>
            <t id="23">AEGS Idris-K</t>
            <t id="24">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Idris-K is an aftermarket special edition of the Idris-P that features additional equipments tailored to dealing with the swarm threat of carrier-type ships. Compared to the Idris-P, Idris-K has an additional size 10 laser beam, four point defense turrets that replaced the remote turrets, and a missile turret that replaced a manned turret. Both Idris-P and Idris-M can be converted to this variant using the aftermarket kit. It can carry two medium fighters in its main hangar as standard complement, plus an Argo MPUV-1C in a dedicated bay.</t>
            <t id="25">ANVL Arrow</t>
            <t id="26">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil Arrow is an agile, light fighter that is prized for its velocity and dexterity. The Arrow boasts advanced thruster tech, a generous weapons package, and an ultra-aerodynamic frame to outmaneuver and outwit its opponents.</t>
            <t id="27">AEGS Eclipse</t>
            <t id="28">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Eclipse is a mid-range stealth bomber designed for tactical torpedo strikes on installations or large ships. Concealed engines and internally-stored weapons allow the Eclipse to stealthily deliver its payload with a minimum of risk of counter-attack. After extensive service with the UEE, this high-tech military equipment is making its debut on the civilian market for 2947.</t>
            <t id="29">CRUS Starlifter C2</t>
            <t id="30">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: CRUS&amp;#xA; Description: The C2 Hercules Starlifter is a civilian heavy transport manufactured by Crusader Industries. Utilizing the patented Hercules military-grade spaceframe and expanding cargo capacity, while sacrificing barely any firepower, the C2 has taken the private sector by storm. It has become the industry standard for racing teams, ship dealers and manufacturers, construction orgs, mining corporations, and even large-scale touring entertainment outfits.</t>
            <t id="31">CRUS Starlifer A2</t>
            <t id="32">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: CRUS&amp;#xA; Description: The A2 Hercules Starlifter is a military heavy gunship and bomber manufactured by Crusader Industries. The A2 gunship has been used to devastating effect in airborne assaults, search and rescue operations, and landing initiatives. With more than double the firepower of the M2, and a custom bomb bay capable of delivering a staggering payload, the A2 caters to anyone hauling massive amounts of cargo through potentially unfriendly skies.</t>
            <t id="33">CRUS Starlifter M2</t>
            <t id="34">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: CRUS&amp;#xA; Description: The M2 Hercules Starlifter is a military protean vehicle transport that supports strategic lift and landing operations (i.e. Sword of Hope). It is manufactured by Crusader Industries. It is the UEE's premier tactical starlifter. The ship's potent combination of capacity, maneuverability, and durability make it the obvious choice in large-scale transport, and a robust weapons package assures your cargo, and crew, gets to where they're going in one piece.</t>
            <t id="35">ANVL F7A</t>
            <t id="36">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The?F7A Hornet?is the?UEE Navy's?premier carrier-based fighter craft, it is the front-line attack ship for military combat missions. While not outfitted for long range runs, the Hornet can take her share of hits and dish out a consistent, powerful response.&amp;#xA; </t>
            <t id="37">ANVL F7C</t>
            <t id="38">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil Aerospace F7C Hornet is the civilian version of the classic F7A Hornet, the carrier-based medium fighter utilized by UEE Navy. It is a multi-purpose fighter and is heavily redesigned to fit non-military components. </t>
            <t id="39">ANVL F7CR</t>
            <t id="40">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil F7C-R Hornet Tracker Mk I is the scanner variant of the F7C Hornet. It boasts an advanced radar suite making it ideal for deep-space explorers who require depth and accuracy in their scan packages. Local militia and larger merc units will also repurpose Trackers to act as mobile Command &amp; Control ships for their squadrons.</t>
            <t id="41">ANVL F7CM</t>
            <t id="42">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil F7C-M Super Hornet Mk I is designed to closely resemble the military load-out while still adhering to civilian regulations. It features the reattachment of the ball turret and incorporates nearly military-grade components. By introducing a second seat to divide logistical and combat responsibilities, the Super Hornet becomes an exceptionally formidable adversary. This enhancement demonstrates the effectiveness of teamwork and makes engaging with the Super Hornet a truly daunting prospect.</t>
            <t id="43">CRUS Starfighter</t>
            <t id="44">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: CRUS&amp;#xA; Description: The Ares Star Fighter is an anti-capital fighter manufactured by Crusader Industries. Designed to lead the charge against capital ships and heavily armed flotillas, the Ares ION excels at spearheading a fleet of fighters and support ships. Its purpose-built Behring SF7E laser cannon accurately delivers high-powered shots to quickly disable the shields of gunships and, with the support of other Ares variants, efficiently incapacitate capital-class vessels. While formidable on its own, the Inferno is an effective complement to the Ares Ion in capital ship engagements, as its armor-piercing rounds can be paired with the Ion's shield-disabling shots. This combination enhances the Inferno's effectiveness in hunting down capital ships.</t>
            <t id="45">AEGS Sabre</t>
            <t id="46">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Sabre was designed as a space superiority fighter for those situations where you need to leave a lighter footprint. It is a part of Aegis' Phase Two of new ship models. Designed to be a rapid responder, the Sabre is more than capable of establishing battlefield dominance for any number of combat scenarios.</t>
            <t id="47">ESPR Talon</t>
            <t id="48">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ESPR&amp;#xA; Description: The Esperia Talon is a small and light single-seat fighter designed for escort services and targeted strikes. Built in the Tevarin style, the Talon has powerful, directional &quot;Phalanx&quot; shields for maximum maneuverability, but weak physical armor once the shields are dropped. A pair of Size 4 weapons and a size 3 missile rack complement the Talon's &quot;strike first and strike hard&quot; combat style.</t>
            <t id="49">AEGS Gladius</t>
            <t id="50">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The P5G Gladius is a light fighter produced by Aegis. Its first design was introduced in 2579 as a replacement for the Stiletto and has been updated over the years to keep up with modern technology. In military circles, the Gladius is beloved for its performance and its simplicity. A fast, light fighter with a laser-focus on dogfighting, the Gladius is an ideal interceptor or escort ship.</t>
            <t id="51">AEGS Vanguard</t>
            <t id="52">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis A3G Vanguard Warden is a long-range military fighter which features extensive forward-mounted weaponry designed to tear through the shields and armor of other spacecraft. So-named because their multiple-jump range allows them to form the vanguard of any military expedition, Vanguards have seen extensive service against the Vanduul.</t>
            <t id="53">DRAK Cutlass</t>
            <t id="54">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: DRAK&amp;#xA; Description: The Drake Cutlass Black is a low-cost, easy-to-maintain solution for local in-system militia units. The larger-than-average cargo hold, Radar intercept officer (RIO) back-seat and dedicated tractor mount are, the company literature insists, for facilitating search and rescue operations. The Cutlass Black is very popular among pirates.</t>
            <t id="55">RSIN Constellation Andromeda</t>
            <t id="56">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: RSI&amp;#xA; Description: The Constellation Andromeda is a multi-person freighter manufactured by Roberts Space Industries (RSI). It is the base model of the Constellation series. It comes with a P-52 Merlin docked at the stern as a snub fighter.</t>
            <t id="57">KRIG P52 merlin</t>
            <t id="58">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: KRIG&amp;#xA; Description: The?Kruger?P-52 Merlin?is a?snub fighter?originally designed to pair with the?RSIN Constellation. Boasting a centerline Gatling cannon and a?Lightning Power?engine, the Merlin is a fast, maneuverable ship that packs a surprising punch! Ideal for?racing, local reconnaissance and fast combat.</t>
            <t id="59">AEGS Reclaimer</t>
            <t id="60">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Reclaimer is an industrial salvage ship. Equipped with a reinforced cargo bay, a long-range jump drive and launch pods for unmanned drones, the Reclaimer is an ideal ship for taking advantage of deep space wrecks. Tractor beams, floodlights, scanner options and docking ports round out the tools on this capable, utilitarian spacecraft.</t>
            <t id="61">AEGS Avenger Titan</t>
            <t id="62">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Avenger Titan is the base variant of the Avenger. With the extra cargo space and the Avenger's tried and true combat abilities, the Titan is a light cargo hauler that's more than capable of handling itself in a fight.[1] The Avenger Titan's loadout is nearly identical to the Stalker, with only the wingtip Suckerpunch cannons being replaced.</t>
            <t id="63">CRUS A1 Spirit</t>
            <t id="64">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: CRUS&amp;#xA; Description: The A1 Spirit is a mid-size multi-purpose light bomber manufactured by Crusader Industries. It is equipped with a payload of ten rapidly-deploying bombs and a strong set of weapons, the Spirit is capable of a wide variety of combat tasks.</t>
            <t id="65">CRUS C1 Spirit</t>
            <t id="66">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: CRUS&amp;#xA; Description: The C1 Spirit is a Medium-size hauler with a focus on versatility and flexible design. Equipped with a generous 64SCU and a rear-mounted tractor beam, the C1 Spirit is a versatile everyday ship for Citizens in the 'verse.</t>
            <t id="67">ANVL Carrack</t>
            <t id="68">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil Carrack is a multi-crew explorer that has more than earned its long-standing status as the go-to pathfinder for both military and civilian services. The Carrack comes with two additional craft - Anvil's own specially designed Pisces snub, and an RSI Ursa Rover.[1] It is built as a single, self-sustaining ship that can make long-duration voyages through the roughest areas of space. It's designed specifically for transiting jump points, dealing with extreme conditions in space and getting back home.</t>
            <t id="69">AEGS Redeemer</t>
            <t id="70">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Redeemer is a gunship that is dotted with turrets and missiles. Equipped with strong shielding and a plethora of weapon systems, this ship can engage a wide range of enemies in patrol, front-line or escort roles.</t>
            <t id="71">ARGO Mole</t>
            <t id="72">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ARGO&amp;#xA; Description: The?Argo?MOLE?(Multi Operator Laser Extractor) is a medium-sized multi-crew?mining?ship. With three independent mining turrets and comprehensive crew facilities, it is a ship perfect for efficient multi-crew mining. In addition, a large array of 24 mineral pods ensures that nothing valuable will ever be left behind. The MOLE lives by the adage &quot;many hands make for light work&quot;</t>
            <t id="73">RSIN Polaris</t>
            <t id="74">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: RSI&amp;#xA; Description: The Polaris is a corvette-class capital ship developed by Roberts Space Industries (RSI) for the United Empire of Earth Navy (UEEN). Designed for use as both a naval patrol ship and to serve as the flagship of civilian militia operations, the Polaris has the capacity to perform search &amp; rescue operations, strike missions and general security patrols. While intended for combat situations, the Polaris can also operate as a command center while providing refuel and repair capabilities from its single small fighter bay.&amp;#xA; &amp;#xA; </t>
            <t id="75">MISC Prospector</t>
            <t id="76">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: MISC&amp;#xA; Description: The Prospector is a small sized mining ship manufactured by MISC. Designed as a single person operated vessel, it features a telescopic mining arm with interchangeable lasers, with 4 detachable collapsible ore storage containers and comfortable living quarters.</t>
            <t id="77">ANVL C8X Pisces</t>
            <t id="78">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: ANVL&amp;#xA; Description: The Anvil C8 Pisces is a small scout ship that comes with the Carrack. It is able to be launched from the hangar bay of the Carrack. The ship was originally sold with the Carrack, and is currently not available standalone. The ship is meant for scouting, reconnaissance and exploring environments inaccessible to the Carrack. Apart from the pilot seat, it also features two additional jump seats for extra passengers. It also contains space for 4 SCU of cargo. Additionally, while it doesn't come equipped with one standard, the ship can also be equipped with a Jump Module.</t>
            <t id="79">DRAK Caterpillar</t>
            <t id="80">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: DRAK&amp;#xA; Description: The Drake Caterpillar is a large, modular cargo ship with a focus on significant capacity and flexibility. It is commonly used for legitimate commerce, extended search, and rescue missions. However, because of the low cost and popularity among civilians, the Caterpillar is known for being used by pirates as the storage location for their ill-gotten gains.</t>
            <t id="81">BANU Defender</t>
            <t id="82">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: BANU&amp;#xA; Description: The Banu Defender is a small two-seat combat ship utilized by the Banu to provide protection and fly alongside the Merchantman. Its design features Xi'an thrusters, Tevarin shields, and four Singe tachyon cannons. As a result, with a light-weight hull, it allows the ship to be agile and fast. Though cargo space is limited, the Defender features modest accommodations for its crew and provides easy access to components.</t>
            <t id="83">AEGS Sabre Raven</t>
            <t id="84">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Aegis Sabre Raven is the high tech variant of the Sabre designed for intelligence missions. Unlike usual variants, it features a redesigned hull that cuts down the wide wingspan of the original Sabre to a smaller profile.</t>
            <t id="85">AEGS Sabre Firebird</t>
            <t id="86">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Sabre Firebird is a medium fighter manufactured by Aegis Dynamics. Designed for swift and relentless assaults using its customized missile system, this high-velocity combat aircraft excels in launching rapid barrages. Its primary objective is to neutralize potential dangers swiftly, leaving adversaries with minimal time to respond. This versatile fighter is equally proficient in embarking on extended-range missions or swiftly mobilizing to safeguard your operational headquarters.</t>
            <t id="87">AEGS Sabre Peregrine</t>
            <t id="88">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: AEGS&amp;#xA; Description: The Sabre Peregrine is a medium racing ship manufactured by Aegis Dynamics. The Peregrine represents the pinnacle of speed among Sabre models, utilizing the renowned military-derived Sabre chassis and refining it for unparalleled velocity. This already aerodynamic structure is enhanced by custom thrusters and meticulously optimized engines, propelling the Peregrine's straight-line speed into an entirely new category.</t>
            <t id="89">VNCL Blade</t>
            <t id="90">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: VNCL&amp;#xA; Description: The Vanduul Blade (UEE designation) is a light carrier-based fighter with high maneuverability that is often used as scouts and first wave assault crafts. With over a quarter-millennia of recorded encounters, it is both one of the first of the species' spacecraft encountered by the United Empire of Earth and one of the most common. Blades are Over the decade of conflict, it has been increasingly used to take out comm arrays and early warning systems. It has also served well as skirmisher units due to their speed allowing them to chase down any ships attempting to flee the area.</t>
            <t id="91">VNCL Glaive</t>
            <t id="92">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: VNCL&amp;#xA; Description: The Vanduul Glaive (UEE designation) is a medium fighter that resemble the symmetrical version of the Scythe. Generally flown by Vanduul with more combat experience, they are better armed and have two huge blades/wings as opposed to one on the standard Scythe.</t>
            <t id="93">VNCL Scythe</t>
            <t id="94">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Manufacturer: VNCL&amp;#xA; Description: The Vanduul Scythe (UEE designation) is a medium fighter that appears in every Vanduul raid. There is not a single allowance for comfort, cargo or anything that would dilute the ship's function as a dedicated dogfighter. Featuring a hefty weapons payload, the Scythe's real asset is its maneuverability, found in the twin main and twelve maneuvering thrusters.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996669" title="missile" descr="missile" voice="no">
            <t id="1">AEGS 蜂鸟反战机导弹</t>
            <t id="2">AEGS 蜂鸟反战机导弹</t>
            <t id="3">S12 PX-12 &quot;Apex&quot;</t>
            <t id="4">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Torpedo&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship torpedo exclusively equipped by Javelin, expensive, but immune to flares.&amp;#xA; Has extremely high damage, medium range, but low speed.</t>
            <t id="5">S9 Argos IX</t>
            <t id="6">Size: S9&amp;#xA; Type: Torpedo&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship torpedo, expensive, but immune to flares.&amp;#xA; Has extremely high damage, medium range, but low speed.</t>
            <t id="7">S2 Ignite II</t>
            <t id="8">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Infrared&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile.&amp;#xA; Has higher speed, longer range, but lower damage.</t>
            <t id="9">S2 Tempest II</t>
            <t id="10">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Crosssection&amp;#xA; Description: Specialized guided Anti-Ship Missile, immune to flares mostly.&amp;#xA; Has medium damage, medium speed, but shorter range.</t>
            <t id="11">S3 Thunderbolt III</t>
            <t id="12">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Electromagnetic&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile.&amp;#xA; Has higher damage, medium range, but slower speed.</t>
            <t id="13">S3 Arrester III</t>
            <t id="14">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Crosssection&amp;#xA; Description: Specialized guided Anti-Ship Missile, immune to flares mostly.&amp;#xA; Has medium damage, medium speed, but shorter range.</t>
            <t id="15">S11 Seeker XI</t>
            <t id="16">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Torpedo&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship torpedo, expensive, but immune to flares.&amp;#xA; Has extremely high damage, medium range, but low speed.</t>
            <t id="17">S8 Scimitar VIII</t>
            <t id="18">Size: S8&amp;#xA; Type: Crosssection&amp;#xA; Description: Specialized guided Anti-Ship Missile, immune to flares mostly.&amp;#xA; Has medium damage, medium speed, but shorter range.</t>
            <t id="19">S1 Spark I</t>
            <t id="20">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Crosssection&amp;#xA; Description: Specialized guided Anti-Ship Missile, immune to flares mostly.&amp;#xA; Has medium damage, medium speed, but shorter range.</t>
            <t id="21">S1 Marksman I</t>
            <t id="22">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Infrared&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile.&amp;#xA; Has higher speed, longer range, but lower damage.</t>
            <t id="23">S1 Taskforce I</t>
            <t id="24">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Electromagnetic&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile.&amp;#xA; Has higher damage, medium range, but slower speed.</t>
            <t id="25">S5 Stormburst Bomb</t>
            <t id="26">Size: S5&amp;#xA; Type: Dumbfire Bomb&amp;#xA; Description: Wreak havoc on ground forces from the Spirit, with the Stormburst. Designed by FireStorm Kinetics to maximize destructive impact at a more moderate size, these S5 bombs feature a mixed composite ordnance to decimate armored targets. The Stormburst also utilizes FireStorm Kinetics' patented Atmo-Xact fins to ensure the payload reaches its target.The bomb itself has no guide system so it requires pilot skill to hit the mark.</t>
            <t id="27">S10 Typhoon X</t>
            <t id="28">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Torpedo&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship torpedo, expensive, but immune to flares.&amp;#xA; Has extremely high damage, medium range, but low speed.</t>
            <t id="29">S2 Dominator II</t>
            <t id="30">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Electromagnetic&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile.&amp;#xA; Has higher damage, medium range, but slower speed.</t>
            <t id="31">S3 Viper III</t>
            <t id="32">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Infrared&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile.&amp;#xA; Has higher speed, longer range, but lower damage.</t>
            <t id="33">S3 Viper III Barrage</t>
            <t id="34">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Infrared&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile, comes with barrage launcher. &amp;#xA; Has higher speed, longer range, but lower damage.</t>
            <t id="35">S3 Arrester III Barrage</t>
            <t id="36">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Crosssection&amp;#xA; Description: Specialized guided Anti-Ship Missile, immune to flares mostly, comes with barrage launcher. &amp;#xA; Has medium damage, medium speed, but shorter range.</t>
            <t id="37">S3 Thunderbolt III Barrage</t>
            <t id="38">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Electromagnetic&amp;#xA; Description: Guided Anti-Ship Missile, comes with barrage launcher. &amp;#xA; Has higher damage, medium range, but slower speed.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996670" title="engine" descr="engine" voice="no">
            <t id="1">AEGS S1 Quantum Engine</t>
            <t id="2">Quantum drives designed for small vessels. They are typically much faster than the travel engines in the X universe.</t>
            <t id="3">AEGS S2 Quantum Engine</t>
            <t id="4">Quantum drives designed for medium vessels. They are typically much faster than the travel engines in the X universe.</t>
            <t id="5">AEGS S3 Quantum Engine</t>
            <t id="6">Quantum drives designed for large vessels. They are typically much faster than the travel engines in the X universe.</t>
            <t id="7">AEGS Capital Quantum Engine</t>
            <t id="8">Quantum drives designed for capital ships. They are typically much faster than the travel engines in the X universe.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996671" title="S" descr="S" voice="no">
            <t id="1">S12 130mm &quot;Shipbuster&quot; Railgun</t>
            <t id="2">Size: S12&amp;#xA; Type: Mass Driver&amp;#xA; Description: The Behring 130mm &quot;Ship Buster&quot; rail gun system is an upcoming size 12 ballistic Ship to Ship weapon. It is the most powerful single-charge rail gun in known space, a hit from a Ship Buster is capable of smashing a destroyer as though it were a tin can. These rail guns use the same technologies as standard fighter-based mass drivers, on a massive scale once thought impossible to achieve. Series of thousands and thousands of charged electromagnets generate the power needed to throw the 130mm slugs.</t>
            <t id="3">AEGS Torpedo Tube</t>
            <t id="4">Size: S9&amp;#xA; Type: Torpedo Launcher&amp;#xA; Description: Torpedo Launcher for devastating AEGS torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="5">AEGS EMP Generator</t>
            <t id="6">Size: S&amp;#xA; Type: EMP Generator&amp;#xA; Description: The EMP Generator can emit a powerful Elecro-Magnetic Pulse (EMP), capable of disable enemy craft within a short range and leaving them vulnerable to attack.</t>
            <t id="7">S Quantum Enforcement</t>
            <t id="8">Size: S&amp;#xA; Type: Quantum Enforcement Device&amp;#xA; Description: Quantum enforcement is the usage of Quantum Enforcement Devices (QEDs) to stall or prevent quantum travel in other ships. Due to the nature of this technology, certain jurisdictions will require licenses or for the operator to be a part of certain organizations.</t>
            <t id="9">M Quantum Enforcement</t>
            <t id="10">Size: M&amp;#xA; Type: Quantum Enforcement Device&amp;#xA; Description: Quantum enforcement is the usage of Quantum Enforcement Devices (QEDs) to stall or prevent quantum travel in other ships. Due to the nature of this technology, certain jurisdictions will require licenses or for the operator to be a part of certain organizations.</t>
            <t id="11">Obervatory</t>
            <t id="12">AEGS S10 GVSR Cannon</t>
            <t id="13">Size: S10&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: The Behring GVSR Repeater is an exclusive Ship to Ship repeater for the Vanguard series. Due to its excellent performance and exclusivity, engineers have managed to increase its caliber and improve the mounting, allowing it to be widely deployed on space stations or large ships as fixed defense measures.</t>
            <t id="14">AEGS Beam Emitter</t>
            <t id="15">Size: XL&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Beam&amp;#xA; Description: Huge deadly beam emitter equipped on Retribution-Class Dreadnought.</t>
            <t id="16">S12 130mm &quot;Shipbuster&quot; Railgun Mk.II</t>
            <t id="17">Size: S12&amp;#xA; Type: Mass Driver&amp;#xA; Description: The Behring 130mm Ship Buster rail gun system is an upcoming size 12 ballistic Ship to Ship weapon. It is the most powerful single-charge rail gun in known space, a hit from a Ship Buster is capable of smashing a destroyer as though it were a tin can. These rail guns use the same technologies as standard fighter-based mass drivers, on a massive scale once thought impossible to achieve. Series of thousands and thousands of charged electromagnets generate the power needed to throw the 130mm slugs. The Mk.II version of the weapon has redesigned the firing mechanism, making it even more dangerous and deadly.</t>
            <t id="18">AEGS S11 GVSR Cannon</t>
            <t id="19">Size: S11&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: The Behring GVSR Repeater is an exclusive Ship to Ship repeater for the Vanguard series. Due to its excellent performance and exclusivity, engineers have managed to increase its caliber and improve the mounting, allowing it to be widely deployed on space stations or large ships as fixed defense measures.</t>
            <t id="20">AEGS S5 Spirit Bomb Hatch</t>
            <t id="21">Size: S5&amp;#xA; Type: Bomb Hatch&amp;#xA; Description: Hauls and deploys the Stormburst bomb.</t>
            <t id="22">AEGS S3 Concentrated Mining Device</t>
            <t id="23">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Mining Beam&amp;#xA; Description: Provides faster mining speed than normal mining device.</t>
            <t id="24">AEGS S6 LS-10 Flak</t>
            <t id="25">Size: S6&amp;#xA; Type: Ballistic Gatling&amp;#xA; Description: Ballistic Gatling. Widely used as AA guns on large vessels.</t>
            <t id="26">AEGS S10 GVSR Cannon</t>
            <t id="27">Size: S10&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: The Behring GVSR Repeater is an exclusive Ship to Ship repeater for the Vanguard series. Due to its excellent performance and exclusivity, engineers have managed to increase its caliber and improve the mounting, allowing it to be widely deployed on space stations or large ships as fixed defense measures.</t>
            <t id="28">Pad</t>
            <t id="29">AEGS S2 Mining Laser</t>
            <t id="30">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Mining Beam&amp;#xA; Description: Standard mining laser used by AEGS ships.</t>
            <t id="31">AEGS Stealth System</t>
            <t id="32">AEGS Stealth System</t>
            <t id="33">AEGS Long-range detection system&amp;#xA; </t>
            <t id="34">AEGS Long-range detection system&amp;#xA; </t>
            <t id="35">Shipboard Artificial Intelligence - Collin</t>
            <t id="36">Basic Shipboard Refinery</t>
            <t id="37">Medium Shipboard Maintenance System</t>
            <t id="38">Basic Shipboard Maintenance System</t>
            <t id="39">This type of ship has not yet been equipped with a shipboard construction system.</t>
            <t id="40">Activate construction system</t>
            <t id="41">Activate the shipboard construction system and automatically send out trade orders to replenish the shortage of materials. Update every minute.</t>
            <t id="42">AEGS Barrage Missile Launcher</t>
            <t id="43">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Barrage Missile Launcher&amp;#xA; Description: Hauls and Launches AEGS Size 3 Barrage Missile. Barrage Missile launches missile in burst fire mode but has longer cooldown.</t>
            <t id="44">Xenon Canon</t>
            <t id="45">Xenon Canon</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996668" title="missile_weapon" descr="missile_weapon" voice="no">
            <t id="1">AEGS S1 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="2">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="3">AEGS S2 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="4">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="5">AEGS S3 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="6">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="7">AEGS S4 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="8">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="9">AEGS S5 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="10">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="11">AEGS S6 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="12">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="13">AEGS S7 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="14">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="15">AEGS S8 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="16">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="17">AEGS S9 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="18">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="19">AEGS S10 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="20">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="21">AEGS S11 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="22">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
            <t id="23">AEGS S12 Missile Rack</t>
            <t id="24">Missile Rack for AEGS missiles/Torpedoes.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996673" title="cannon_weapon" descr="cannon_weapon" voice="no">
            <t id="1">S10 Destroyer Mass Driver</t>
            <t id="2">Size: S10&amp;#xA; Type: Mass Driver&amp;#xA; Description: The K&amp;W Destroyer Mass Driver Cannon is a size 10 mass driver cannon. It is the railgun equipped on the Idris-M.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996674" title="beam_weapon" descr="beam_weapon" voice="no">
            <t id="1">S10 Exodus Laser Beam</t>
            <t id="2">Size: S10&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Beam&amp;#xA; Description:The Hurston Dynamics Exodus Laser Beam is a size 10 vehicle laser beam. The weapon is mounted to the empty S10 on an Idris-P as part of an Idris-K conversion kit.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996667" title="turret" descr="turret" voice="no">
            <t id="1">AEGS S2 CF-227 Badger</t>
            <t id="2">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: The CF-227 Badger is Klaus &amp; Werner's dependable size two repeating laser. Its increased output and high rate of fire make it a solid contender in any fight.</t>
            <t id="3">AEGS S3 CF-337 Panther</t>
            <t id="4">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: The CF-337 Panther is the size three model in Klaus &amp; Werner's laser repeater line. The Panther is a true fire-and-forget weapon with a respectable power consumption-to-damage ratio. Pilots who outfit their ships with Panthers rarely regret the decision.</t>
            <t id="5">AEGS S4 CF-447 Rhino</t>
            <t id="6">Size: S4&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: When a ship comes charging at you with a CF-447 Rhino strapped on, it is an experience few pilots will ever forget. This formidable size four laser repeater from Klaus &amp; Werner is well suited for medium-range engagements, but packs a wallop up close.</t>
            <t id="7">AEGS S5 CF-557 Galdereen</t>
            <t id="8">Size: S5&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: With a bite as fearsome as its fanged namesake, the Klaus &amp; Werner CF-557 Galdereen laser repeater is a solid choice for a wide range of vehicles thanks to its high rate of fire and consistent efficacy.</t>
            <t id="9">AEGS S6 CF-667 Mammoth</t>
            <t id="10">Size: S6&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: This beast of a laser repeater from Klaus &amp; Werner features three massive barrels that warn any who spot a ship bearing the CF-667 that they may want to think again before engaging.</t>
            <t id="11">AEGS S7 Attrition-7</t>
            <t id="12">Size: S7&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: Hurston Dynamics' Attrition series is more than just a simple laser repeater; it features advanced cascade technology that allows the weapon to maintain its performance while sustaining its energy output.</t>
            <t id="13">AEGS S8 Attrition-8</t>
            <t id="14">Size: S8&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: Hurston Dynamics' Attrition series is more than just a simple laser repeater; it features advanced cascade technology that allows the weapon to maintain its performance while sustaining its energy output.</t>
            <t id="23">AEGS S2 M4A</t>
            <t id="24">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The M4A is Behring's second tier laser autocannon. Its bigger size means more power consumption in exchange for packing a bigger punch. Fire rate and power efficiency are comparable to the M3A model.</t>
            <t id="25">AEGS S3 M5A</t>
            <t id="26">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The M5A is Behring's third tier laser autocannon. Its bigger size means more power consumption in exchange for packing a bigger punch. Fire rate and power efficiency are comparable to the M4A model.</t>
            <t id="27">AEGS S4 M6A</t>
            <t id="28">Size: S4&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The M6A is Behring's fourth tier laser autocannon. Its bigger size means more power consumption in exchange for packing a bigger punch. Fire rate and power efficiency are comparable to the M5A model.</t>
            <t id="29">AEGS S5 M7A</t>
            <t id="30">Size: S5&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The M7A is Behring's fifth tier laser autocannon. Its bigger size means more power consumption in exchange for packing a bigger punch. Fire rate and power efficiency are comparable to the M6A model.</t>
            <t id="31">AEGS S6 M8A</t>
            <t id="32">Size: S6&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The M8A is Behring's sixth tier laser autocannon. Its bigger size means more power consumption in exchange for packing a bigger punch. Fire rate and power efficiency are comparable to the M7A model.</t>
            <t id="33">AEGS S7 M9A</t>
            <t id="34">Size: S7&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The M9A is Behring's seventh tier laser autocannon. Its bigger size means more power consumption in exchange for packing a bigger punch. Fire rate and power efficiency are comparable to the M8A model.</t>
            <t id="35">AEGS S8 Omnisky XX</t>
            <t id="36">Size: S8&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The Omnisky series is the laser autocannon from manufacturer A&amp;R. It boasts increased damage and range and power consumption over other laser weapons, and utilizes many of the same components resulting in good weapon efficiency.</t>
            <t id="37">AEGS S9 Omnisky XXI</t>
            <t id="38">Size: S9&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: The Omnisky series is the laser autocannon from manufacturer A&amp;R. It boasts increased damage and range and power consumption over other laser weapons, and utilizes many of the same components resulting in good weapon efficiency.</t>
            <t id="10001">AEGS S2 Missile Turret</t>
            <t id="10002">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Missile Turret&amp;#xA; Description: Standard fixed missile defence.</t>
            <t id="10003">AEGS S3 Missile Turret</t>
            <t id="10004">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Missile Turret&amp;#xA; Description: Standard fixed missile defence.</t>
            <t id="20001">AEGS S2 NN-14</t>
            <t id="20002">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Neutron Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: MaxOx's NN-14 neutron cannon offers a massive energy payload at the expense of speed and energy efficiency. One could argue the virtues of speed, rate of fire and distance over damage, but the argument becomes irrelevant if you only need to hit them once.</t>
            <t id="20003">AEGS S3 NN-15</t>
            <t id="20004">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Neutron Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: MaxOx's NN-15 neutron cannon offers a massive energy payload at the expense of speed and energy efficiency. One could argue the virtues of speed, rate of fire and distance over damage, but the argument becomes irrelevant if you only need to hit them once.</t>
            <t id="20005">AEGS S2 NDB-28</t>
            <t id="20006">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Neutron Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: Featuring a sleek, scientific design, the MaxOx NDB series is the next step in serious stopping power. Twin barrels overlap blasts for sustained neutron fire that remains effective at short to medium range.</t>
            <t id="20007">AEGS S3 NDB-30</t>
            <t id="20008">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Neutron Repeater&amp;#xA; Description: Featuring a sleek, scientific design, the MaxOx NDB series is the next step in serious stopping power. Twin barrels overlap blasts for sustained neutron fire that remains effective at short to medium range.</t>
            <t id="20009">AEGS S2 FL-22</t>
            <t id="20010">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: Deliver massive damage from a distance with Kroneg's FL line of laser cannons. The size two FL-22 shines at medium and long ranges thanks to a design that minimizes damage falloff.</t>
            <t id="20011">AEGS S3 FL-33</t>
            <t id="20012">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Laser Cannon&amp;#xA; Description: Deliver massive damage from a distance with Kroneg's FL line of laser cannons. The size three FL-33 shines at medium and long ranges thanks to a design that minimizes damage falloff.</t>
            <t id="20013">0</t>
            <t id="20014">0</t>
            <t id="20015">0</t>
            <t id="20016">0</t>
            <t id="30001">AEGS S9 AD9B</t>
            <t id="30002">The ADXB series, Behring's take on the classic ballistic gatling, includes a crystal cycle firing mechanism in the the high speed rotary system to maximize efficiency for sustained engagements with minimal misfires. Next time an aggressor escalates a hostile situation, make them regret the decision by spinning up this overwhelming and effective weapon.</t>
            <t id="30003">AEGS S2 GT-215</t>
            <t id="30004">The Mantis GT-215 is a hydraulically-driven Gatling-type rotary cannon designed to deliver smaller rounds at a very high rate of fire. The Mantis is designed to shred armor on very fast targets, sacrificing power for absolute saturation of the target area.</t>
            <t id="30005">AEGS S3 GT-220</t>
            <t id="30006">The Mantis GT-220 is a hydraulically-driven Gatling-type rotary cannon designed to deliver smaller rounds at a very high rate of fire. The Mantis is designed to shred armor on very fast targets, sacrificing power for absolute saturation of the target area.</t>
            <t id="30007">AEGS S4 AD4B</t>
            <t id="30008">The ADXB series, Behring's take on the classic ballistic gatling, includes a crystal cycle firing mechanism in the the high speed rotary system to maximize efficiency for sustained engagements with minimal misfires. Next time an aggressor escalates a hostile situation, make them regret the decision by spinning up this overwhelming and effective weapon.</t>
            <t id="30009">AEGS S5 AD5B</t>
            <t id="30010">The ADXB series, Behring's take on the classic ballistic gatling, includes a crystal cycle firing mechanism in the the high speed rotary system to maximize efficiency for sustained engagements with minimal misfires. Next time an aggressor escalates a hostile situation, make them regret the decision by spinning up this overwhelming and effective weapon.</t>
            <t id="30011">AEGS S6 AD6B</t>
            <t id="30012">The ADXB series, Behring's take on the classic ballistic gatling, includes a crystal cycle firing mechanism in the the high speed rotary system to maximize efficiency for sustained engagements with minimal misfires. Next time an aggressor escalates a hostile situation, make them regret the decision by spinning up this overwhelming and effective weapon.</t>
            <t id="30013">AEGS S7 AD7B</t>
            <t id="30014">The ADXB series, Behring's take on the classic ballistic gatling, includes a crystal cycle firing mechanism in the the high speed rotary system to maximize efficiency for sustained engagements with minimal misfires. Next time an aggressor escalates a hostile situation, make them regret the decision by spinning up this overwhelming and effective weapon.</t>
            <t id="30015">AEGS S8 AD8B</t>
            <t id="30016">The ADXB series, Behring's take on the classic ballistic gatling, includes a crystal cycle firing mechanism in the the high speed rotary system to maximize efficiency for sustained engagements with minimal misfires. Next time an aggressor escalates a hostile situation, make them regret the decision by spinning up this overwhelming and effective weapon.</t>
            <t id="30031">AEGS S2 SW16BR2</t>
            <t id="30032">The SW16BR2 Sawbuck is Behring's contribution to the expanding Ballistic Repeater market. Its sequential-firing double barrel configuration offers an effective middle-ground for operators looking for a higher rate of fire than a cannon, but without the fear of overheating that you would get with a gatling.</t>
            <t id="30033">AEGS S3 SW16BR3</t>
            <t id="30034">The SW16BR3 Shredder is Behring's contribution to the expanding Ballistic Repeater market. Its sequential-firing double barrel configuration offers an effective middle-ground for operators looking for a higher rate of fire than a cannon, but without the fear of overheating that you would get with a gatling.</t>
            <t id="30035">AEGS S2 Suckerpunch-L</t>
            <t id="30036">Silently strike from afar with the Suckerpunch. Joker's long-range size two distortion cannon drains a target's shield system, leaving them helpless to defend against what you have planned next. An ideal choice for law enforcement, bounty hunters, and other non-lethal operations.</t>
            <t id="30037">AEGS S3 Suckerpunch-XL</t>
            <t id="30038">Silently strike from afar with the Suckerpunch. Joker's long-range size three distortion cannon drains a target's shield system, leaving them helpless to defend against what you have planned next. An ideal choice for law enforcement, bounty hunters, and other non-lethal operations.</t>
            <t id="30045">AEGS S2 10-Series Greatsword</t>
            <t id="30046">KnightBridge Arms knows that when it comes to battle, having the right weapon can make all the difference. With its powerful ballistic rounds, the versatile, size two 10-Series Greatsword will see you through to the conflict's end thanks to it long range and high damage potential.</t>
            <t id="30047">AEGS S3 11-Series Broadsword</t>
            <t id="30048">KnightBridge Arms knows that when it comes to battle, having the right weapon can make all the difference. With its powerful ballistic rounds, the versatile, size two 11-Series Broadsword will see you through to the conflict's end thanks to it long range and high damage potential.</t>
            <t id="40001">AEGS S3 Revenant</t>
            <t id="40002">If it ain't broke, don't fix it. And if you want it broke, aim a Revenant at it. Solidly built on a foundation of centuries-old tech, Apocalypse Arms puts an innovative spin on battle-tested designs to create a rugged ballistic Gatling that can steadily hurtle death across the void. Though it's slow to spin up and cool down, the Revenant's dependability makes it a favorite for those expecting to find trouble.</t>
            <t id="40003">AEGS S4 Revenant</t>
            <t id="40004">If it ain't broke, don't fix it. And if you want it broke, aim a Revenant at it. Solidly built on a foundation of centuries-old tech, Apocalypse Arms puts an innovative spin on battle-tested designs to create a rugged ballistic Gatling that can steadily hurtle death across the void. Though it's slow to spin up and cool down, the Revenant's dependability makes it a favorite for those expecting to find trouble.</t>
            <t id="50001">AEGS S7 SF7E</t>
            <t id="50002">SF7E is integrated within the frame of the Ares. It is designed to take on capital-class ships. Because of the nature of a large weapon being attached to a small ship, the weapon itself is built with an additional power plant, shield and cooler.</t>
            <t id="50003">AEGS S7 SF7B</t>
            <t id="50004">Slug it out with large spacecraft and swiftly shred smaller ships with the SF7B ballistic Gatling. Built specifically for the Ares, the weapon seamlessly integrates into the body of the ship. The weapon's impressive rate of fire unleashes high-density rounds that tear through armor and shields, making it a perfect choice for situations where target saturation is key.</t>
            <t id="60001">AEGS S4 C-788</t>
            <t id="60002">Hurtling high caliber rounds with devastating velocity, Behring's C-788 Ballistic Autocannon was built to punch through ship armor, it also has huge AoE. Extremely durable with exceptional heat resistance, the &quot;Combine&quot; can handle a heavy workload that, even with the weapon's slower rate of fire, makes it an ideal choice for taking on larger, less maneuverable targets.</t>
            <t id="70001">AEGS S2 Deadbolt II</t>
            <t id="70002">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70003">AEGS S3 Deadbolt III</t>
            <t id="70004">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70005">AEGS S4 Deadbolt IV</t>
            <t id="70006">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70007">AEGS S5 Deadbolt V</t>
            <t id="70008">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70009">AEGS S6 Deadbolt VI</t>
            <t id="70010">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70011">AEGS S7 Deadbolt VII</t>
            <t id="70012">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70013">AEGS S8 Deadbolt VIII</t>
            <t id="70014">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="70015">AEGS S9 Deadbolt IX</t>
            <t id="70016">Spread dread with the Deadbolt ballistic cannon. Feared for its firepower at short range, this notorious Tevarin weapon earned its intimidating reputation during the First Tevarin War as part of the Tevarin fleet's devastating arsenal. Esperia has painstakingly recreated the Deadbolt out of respect to the original weapon and warriors who used it so effectively.</t>
            <t id="80001">AEGS S7 Sledge-VII</t>
            <t id="80002">The Klaus &amp; Werner Sledge VII Mass Driver Cannon is a hard-hitting ballistic weapon capable of firing multiple types of ammunition. This weapon's increased shield penetration capabilities comes at a cost, however. Magazine space is limited, so ammunition must be replenished regularly. Because it does not use energy-based projectiles, the K&amp;W mass driver has a reduced power cost and therefore results in a reduced EM signature.</t>
            <t id="80003">AEGS S8 Sledge-VIII</t>
            <t id="80004">The Klaus &amp; Werner Sledge VIII Mass Driver Cannon is a hard-hitting ballistic weapon capable of firing multiple types of ammunition. This weapon's increased shield penetration capabilities comes at a cost, however. Magazine space is limited, so ammunition must be replenished regularly. Because it does not use energy-based projectiles, the K&amp;W mass driver has a reduced power cost and therefore results in a reduced EM signature.</t>
            <t id="80005">AEGS S9 Sledge-IX</t>
            <t id="80006">The Klaus &amp; Werner Sledge IX Mass Driver Cannon is a hard-hitting ballistic weapon capable of firing multiple types of ammunition. This weapon's increased shield penetration capabilities comes at a cost, however. Magazine space is limited, so ammunition must be replenished regularly. Because it does not use energy-based projectiles, the K&amp;W mass driver has a reduced power cost and therefore results in a reduced EM signature.</t>
            <t id="90001">AEGS S4 Tarantula GT-870Mk4</t>
            <t id="90002">Fed by Gallenson Tactical's patented SpinGlide drum ammunition system, the Tarantula GT-870 Mk4 can smoothly and accurately deliver a consistent stream of ballistic shells. Though it only has a moderate rate of fire, its trustworthy durability makes it a dependable addition to any fight.</t>
            <t id="90003">AEGS S5 Tarantula GT-870Mk5</t>
            <t id="90004">Fed by Gallenson Tactical's patented SpinGlide drum ammunition system, the Tarantula GT-870 Mk5 can smoothly and accurately deliver a consistent stream of ballistic shells. Though it only has a moderate rate of fire, its trustworthy durability makes it a dependable addition to any fight.</t>
            <t id="90005">AEGS S6 Tarantula GT-870Mk6</t>
            <t id="90006">Fed by Gallenson Tactical's patented SpinGlide drum ammunition system, the Tarantula GT-870 Mk6 can smoothly and accurately deliver a consistent stream of ballistic shells. Though it only has a moderate rate of fire, its trustworthy durability makes it a dependable addition to any fight.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996678" title="aegs shield" descr="aegs shield" voice="no">
            <t id="1">StealthC S3 Akura</t>
            <t id="2">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="3">StealthB S3 Bila</t>
            <t id="4">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="5">StealthA S3 Nargun</t>
            <t id="6">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="7">StealthB S2 Sheut</t>
            <t id="8">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="9">StealthC S2 Obscura</t>
            <t id="10">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="11">StealthA S2 Umbra</t>
            <t id="12">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="13">StealthC S1 Shimmer</t>
            <t id="14">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="15">StealthB S1 Vell</t>
            <t id="16">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="17">StealthA S1 Mirage</t>
            <t id="18">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Stealth&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Stealth/civilian shields offer a smaller amount of shield capacity, striking a balance between shield regeneration and delay, and they are cost-effective.&amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="19">MillitaryC S3 Sukoran</t>
            <t id="20">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="21">MillitaryB S3 FullBlock</t>
            <t id="22">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="23">MillitaryA S3 FR-86</t>
            <t id="24">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="25">MillitaryC S2 FullStop</t>
            <t id="26">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="27">MillitaryB S2 CoverAll</t>
            <t id="28">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="29">MillitaryA S2 FR-76</t>
            <t id="30">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="31">MillitaryC S1 AllStop</t>
            <t id="32">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="33">MillitaryB S1 ForceWall</t>
            <t id="34">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="35">MillitaryA S1 FR-66</t>
            <t id="36">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Military-grade shields have the highest shield regeneration rate during combat, providing a substantial shield pool for combat vessels.&amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="37">IndustrialC S3 Stronghold</t>
            <t id="38">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="39">IndustrialB S3 Barbican</t>
            <t id="40">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="41">IndustrialA S3 Parapet</t>
            <t id="42">Size: S3&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="43">IndustrialC S2 Aspis</t>
            <t id="44">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="45">IndustrialB S2 Citadel</t>
            <t id="46">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="47">IndustrialA S2 Rampart</t>
            <t id="48">Size: S2&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="49">IndustrialC S1 Bulwark</t>
            <t id="50">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: C&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade C shields retain the characteristics of the shield while significantly reducing costs, making them suitable for novice pilots.</t>
            <t id="51">IndustrialB S1 Guardian</t>
            <t id="52">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: B&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade B shields represent a compromise between price and performance, offering better value for money compared to other classes of shields.</t>
            <t id="53">IndustrialA S1 Pallsade</t>
            <t id="54">Size: S1&amp;#xA; Type: Industrial&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Industrial Shields have highest default Shield Value, but lower recharge speed or longer recharge delay. &amp;#xA; Grade A shields are expensive, but this level of equipment represents the pinnacle of technology, providing the most advanced performance for the ship.</t>
            <t id="55">MillitaryA C FR-96</t>
            <t id="56">Size: Capital&amp;#xA; Type: Military&amp;#xA; Grade: A&amp;#xA; Description: Capital class shields are mostly specially customized for ships. They provide comprehensive protection for capital vessels.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996675" title="aegs help" descr="aegs help" voice="no">
            <t id="1">Only C8X Pisces class can dock here.</t>
            <t id="2">Only the following M-size ships are allowed to dock: Hammerhead, Carrack, Caterpillar, Constellation, Mole, Redeemer, Avenger, Spirit, Hercules.</t>
            <t id="3">Only the following M-class ships are allowed to dock: Constellation, Mole, Redeemer, Avenger, Spirit.</t>
            <t id="4">The port side deck is occupied, docking denied.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996676" title="aegs research" descr="aegs research" voice="no">
            <t id="1">&quot;Xenon Crisis&quot; Emergency Procedures</t>
            <t id="2">The emergence of the new Xenon warship indicates the weaknesses in the current UEE fleet, and the Empire needs more cutting-edge vessels to counter future crises.</t>
        </page>
        <page id="996677" title="aegs computer" descr="aegs computer" voice="no">
            <t id="1">Unbelievable! You've actually destroyed the Xenon's E!</t>
            <t id="2">You might not believe it! Researchers have picked up a mysterious signal from the damaged E. By deciphering this signal, we can now construct the United Empire of Earth (UEE)'s Punisher-class dreadnought!</t>
            <t id="3">Wow! The Retribution-class is the capital ship we've built at greater cost! To rebuild it, we'll need to collect the mysterious Xenon E signal once again.</t>
            <t id="4">Congratulations! You have successfully built the Retribution-class dreadnought! Now, no one in the known galaxy will be able to challenge our authority!</t>
            <t id="5">Unfortunately, we didn't find anything useful from the wreckage of the Xenon E.</t>
            <t id="6">You might not believe it! His Imperial Majesty, Emperor Ivar Messer, has given his authorization! Now we can build the United Empire of Earth's Retribution-class dreadnought!</t>
        </page>
    </add>

    <add sel="/language[@id='44']/page[@id='20221']">
        <t id="5063">Dreadnought</t>
    </add>
</diff>
